trade65.com 2014-12-26

# Binary Options Trading And Strategy on Trade65

### PRIVACY POLICY FOR USERS

### 1\. Introduction

trade65.com (the "Company" or "we") offers binary options and financial market trading services via the Internet. When you use the Company's services via its online trading platform, you shall be asked to provide personal identifiable information ("Personal Information") to the Company. We are committed to respecting your privacy and to complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws. We have therefore provided this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect, use, store and protect your Personal Information for the purpose of offering you trading services. If you do not understand this Privacy Policy or how we handle or use the Personal Information which you provide to us then you are invited to send in your questions to [support@trade65.com](mailto:support@trade65.com) and we will do our best to answer your questions in full as quickly as possible. You should read this Privacy Policy in conjunction with our End User License Agreement **"Terms"**. 

### 2\. Modifications to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in any applicable data protection and privacy legislation. You agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates and your continued use of the website constitutes your agreement to any amendments made to this Privacy Policy. In the event that the reasons for Personal Information collection change, we will notify you as soon as possible and seek your consent where such notification relates to a new additional purpose for processing. We encourage you to visit this Privacy Policy regularly to check the provisions in force from time to time.

### 3\. Personal Information Collection

We collect Personal Information when you register on the website and use our trading services, make customer inquiries, enter promotions, register for information or other services from the Company or when you respond to communications from us (such as questionnaires or surveys). The Personal Information we will collect from you may include, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, date of birth and other information collected on registration or through surveys which the Company may undertake.

### 4\. How Your Personal Information is Processed ("Purposes")

The Personal Information which you provide to us will be processed for one or more of the following Purposes: (i) to provide services to you; (ii) to confirm financial transactions; (iii) to process any of your requests for information; (iv) to provide member support services to you; (v) to market our services or products; (vi) identification and vetting purposes; (vii) statistical analysis and research; (viii) to notify you about updates to our software and/or services; (ix) to support any of the intended purposes specifically stated at the time at which you provided the Personal Information; and (x) to comply with legal and regulatory requirements.

### 5\. To Whom Your Personal Information is Disclosed ("Recipients")

Your Personal Information may, for the Purposes, be disclosed for processing to any of the following Recipients: (i) to any members of the Company’s group and their employees who have a need to know such information; (ii) to any third parties which provide services to the Company or on its behalf, in order to allow or enable us to provide you with trading services, including by way of example payment processors and data verifiers; (iii) to any third parties who provide the Company services in relation to the operation of its website; (iv) to any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of the Company's business processes; (v) to any potential purchasers or investors in the Company; and (vi) to any third parties with your consent.

Any processing performed by any Recipients will, where required by law, be governed by a data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving any and all of your statutory data protection rights and obligating the Recipients to respect the Personal Information and handle it in accordance with the relevant laws.

We ensure that your information will not be disclosed to government institutions or authorities except if required by law.

### 6\. Your Choice - Direct Marketing

Out of respect for your right to privacy we are happy to provide you with an easy means to opt-out of receiving email offers from us. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers by sending a blank message with the word "Remove" in the subject area to [support@trade65.com](mailto:support@trade65.com). If you would like to stop receiving our mail or telemarketing offers, please call [+357.25.030.415](callto:+35725030415) or write to Gr. Xenopoulou 17, 3106, Limassol, Cyprus.

### 7\. Your Rights in relation to your Personal Information

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. You can write to us at any time to obtain a copy of your Personal Information and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Where appropriate, you may have your Personal Information rectified, amended or completed. In either event, we may require evidence of your identity. In addition, we may charge a small charge to cover the cost of administration.

### 8\. Retention

Your Personal Information will not be stored for longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

### 9\. Security

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard all the Personal Information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your Personal Information, are obliged to respect your privacy. trade65.com does not save or store any Credit Card details.

### 10\. Cookies

We may send you a permanent cookie when you register with us. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit and your navigational activity. Cookies can help us to recognize you when you next visit our website, to gather customer information and evaluate our websites’ advertising and promotional effectiveness and note the other websites you enter via a link from our website. This permits us to tailor the service provided to you.

We may also use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of our website. You are not obliged to accept a cookie from us or from any other website. To enable or disable cookies, follow the instructions provided by your browser. However, for legitimate security reasons, we may refuse access to specific website content unless you accept the use of a cookie or similar device.

### 11\. Protection of Minors

The services provided by the Company are not intended for or directed to minors or persons under the age of legal consent. Any person who provides us with Personal Information represents to us that they are 18 years of age or over the age of legal consent in their jurisdiction. We reserve the right to access and verify any Personal Information submitted by or collected from you. If we become aware that a minor has attempted to or has submitted Personal Information, we may not accept this information and may take steps to remove such information from our records.

Last updated on 23-August-2012

PLEASE PRINT OFF AND RETAIN A HARD COPY OF THIS AGREEMENT FOR YOUR RECORDS.
